nice how's it going so much fun to be
here some of you guys probably recognize
me from the Ellen degenerous show
started working for Ellen and then I had
to grow this beard so they could tell us
apart around the
office you don't have to laugh that hard
at that
one in addition to being a writer I also
have two karate trophies and three
weightlifting trophies cuz I don't know
if you guys know this but you can just
go to the store and buy
trophies there's no test or background
check or anything just pick them up and
impress
people they do use me on Aon Ellen
sometimes but like I've only ever been
recognized in public once and it really
let me know where I fall on the fame
scale cuz I was out at a bar and this
girl comes up to me and she goes oh my
gosh I've seen you on Ellen can I get a
picture with you and I said sure and she
handed me her phone and I tried to get a
selfie of us but nothing happened and I
said oh it says your memory is full
you'll have to delete a picture to make
room and she takes her phone and she
goes m nah
the kind of star power you're dealing
with here in
Provo uh I do something a little bit
different than the other Comics I need
you guys to participate here a little
bit I do improv standup so I can do
stand up based on any suggestion from
the crowd I just need like a word or a
phrase to get me started anything at all
wrestling I think I heard pre-written
material in the
back so I'm glad the pandemic is over
glad the restaurants are open we don't
have to do the takeout and delivery
thing anymore I saw even Golden Corral
had a sign out that said open for
takeout and delivery in case you don't
want covid but still want all the
[Applause]
symptoms like my chest hurts and my
stomach hurts and none of this food
tastes
right I had to buy everything online
during the pandemic I started doing a
lot more online shopping and I found out
whenever you use your credit card online
it always gives you one of these are you
a robot tests you guys all done these it
always ask me one of three questions it
always says choose the pictures that
have traffic lights choose the pictures
that have buses or choose the pictures
that have stop signs so I have no idea
how we're supposed to trust self-driving
cars now that I know the three things
robots cannot
identify
[Applause]
our traffic lights buses and stop sign
how is that the robot test do you think
the robot test would be like choose the
pictures that show irony sadness and
love but instead it's like a DMV exam
it's like choose the pictures that show
Blind pedestrians robots can't see
those my car already has technology on
it that I don't understand like it has
one of these smart radios that tells you
what's playing you know it says Nirvana
when Nirvana comes on and Smashing
Pumpkins when Smashing Pumpkins comes on
and garbage when Cold Play comes
on somehow it
knows I was really glad they decided not
to cancel the college football season
last year cuz I'm a big college football
fan anyone else here nice I I love
college football the one thing I've
never been able to figure out though is
uh how is Army not the best colle
football
team like there's just a bunch of school
students playing football against each
other and then for some reason one of
the teams is the United States
Army the most elite fighting force on
the planet and they're not that
good doesn't make any sense to me how do
you defeat Nazi Germany Soviet Russia
and the Islamic State in Syria then lose
to Western
Kentucky
they've also lost to the Warriors the
Spartans and the Trojans which means
other teams are naming themselves after
armies than beating the actual
[Applause]
Army it's got to be weird for the team
playing the Army because like everything
before the game celebrates the Army
first jets fly over the stadium in honor
of the army then everyone sings the
national anthem in honor of the army
then the announcers is like will
everyone please stand in clap for the
man in seat 3B he was in the Army then
they're like all right now let's
humiliate the army
let beat them 54 to
12 it's true the only branch of the
military with a good football team is
the Air Force but they only have a
ground game it makes no sense at
all done a lot of hiking this last year
I went to Joshua Tree a lot because I
live in Los Angeles and uh I don't do
drugs but I found out whenever you go to
Joshua Tree from Los Angeles people
always say the same thing they go you
have to do mushrooms Joshua tree is
beautiful on mushrooms muss which sounds
like this amazing experience at first
but you know what else is beautiful on
mushrooms your
garage or the bathroom at a
Wendy's everywhere is beautiful on
mushrooms Joshua tree is not doing the
heavy lifting there You' be like oh you
have to see the backseat of my car it's
beautiful this time of year on
mushrooms the whole selling point of
Joshua Tree should be exactly the
opposite she' be like you have to go to
Joshua Tree it's so beautiful you don't
even have to do
mushrooms
no one ever told me anything like that
about other national parks no one's ever
been like oh you have to go to arches
and do
meth although I'm sure some people have
if you've driven down that
way I love visiting in the national
parks you know they're they're beautiful
they showcase like the wonders of nature
that God created for us which is amazing
but I don't know if God would be happy
with like what we've done with the
national parks you know like arches you
know he's like he's like oh I made all
these beautiful stone AR arches for you
what do you call this area and we're
like that's the devil's
garden and he's like oh and what about
all these mountains and canyons I made
for you in California and we're like
Devil's postpile Devil's punch ball
Devil's Canyon Devil's
Backbone he's like and and the rock
formation I made in Wyoming you call it
the like the Lord's Hill or Mount Jesus
and we're like no that's the Devil's
Tower it's like didn't you name anything
after me it's like well in Colorado we
have an called Garden of the Gods he's
like well you tried but you made it
plural like I specifically asked you not
to the only one we named after anything
in the Bible is Joshua tree and we just
use it to do
[Applause]
mushrooms I'm excited for international
travel to open up again the last trip I
took I went to Africa for the first time
it was amazing it was one of the most
amazing trips I've ever been on but it
was the first trip where I had to take
medication before I went I got these U
malaria pills and it said on the bottle
take one pill by mouth daily I was like
you don't have to put by mouth on
there the default Place anyone puts
pills no one guesses another hole
first no one ever gets a bottle of
Tylenol and it's like H doesn't say
where they go I know where I'm going to
stick
these the only time you have to put
instructions on the pill bottle is when
they don't go in your
mouth that's when it has to say take one
pill I'm not taking these
pills I'd rather get
malaria I want to get the covid vaccine
I haven't gotten it yet but like it's
weird because I've never been skeptical
of vaccines and then the harder they try
to push it the more skeptical I get like
I was all on board with it you know like
they used to have a me they had a
measles vaccine I was like yeah I'll get
that then they came out with a tennis
vaccine I'm like yeah I'll get that they
had a Lyme disease vaccine I was like
I'll get that then they came out with
the covid vaccine I'm like yeah I'll get
that and they're like come on we'll give
you free donuts and your rights back and
I'm
[Applause]
like I'm like all right relax I said I'd
get it I'll go to my doctor no don't go
to your doctor just come to Dodger
Stadium we'll give it to you a van in
the parking
[Applause]
lot and I'm like what is in this V
honestly all Joe Biden has to do to get
me to get the vaccine is to go 24 hours
without telling me to get the vaccine
I've literally been on my way out the
door to go to CVS to get the vaccine and
then Joe Biden pops on the TV and goes
you better get the vaccine and I'm like
nope something's
up no no you should get the vaccine I
don't want to get in
trouble they'll put a warning on this on
YouTube
I do hope the economy recovers you know
a lot of people are worried about the
economy right now they're worried about
how they're doing economically how
they're doing financially uh but don't
worry I figured out a perfect way to
tell where you stand economically um it
all depends on how you feel about Red
Lobster if you think Red Lobster is a
fancy restaurant you're not doing well
[Music]
[Laughter]
economically cuz Red Lobster is not a
fancy restaurant it's Applebees plus
Lobster and the thing they're most
famous for is their Cheddar Bay Biscuits
which is weird because if you serve
lobster but you're more famous for the
free bread you left on the
table you are not making the lobster
correctly it's really nice to be back on
the road for standup whenever I'm on the
road I try to travel cheap so I stay at
Motel 6 a
lot and then some nights I'm in the mood
for something a little cleaner and
classier and I just sleep in the car
Motel 6 is like the Red Lobster of
hotels I don't mind staying in a
different Motel every night but then I
have to figure out how a different
shower works every morning which always
makes me feel like I'm a lab rat in some
sort of cruel experiment I'm just
standing there naked and scared in front
of a bunch of buttons and
levers and I know that one of them will
punish me with hot water and one of them
will punish me with cold water but if I
can figure out the code I'll get some
warm
water of course the whole experiment's
being timed cuz if you don't figure it
out by 9:00 a.m. and get downstairs they
take away breakfast and you don't get
any
[Applause]
cheese when I flew in here I got to sit
in the exit row on the plane they always
ask you that question where they're like
are you willing and able to help in an
emergency and I don't know if I could do
it but I always say
yes cuz if I fail no one's going to live
to tell about
it there are no consequences to lying on
that question just go for the leg room
worst case scenario you die slightly
more comfortable than the people behind
you you ever hear someone change their
mind on that question that always puts
you at ease before the flight I was on a
flight and this guy was sitting in front
of me and the flight attendant comes
over and she goes sir are you willing
and able to help in an emergency and he
goes no no and she goes well then I'm
going to have to ask you to move I need
a verbal yes in order to sit here and he
goes okay
yes
really you just temporarily forgot that
you can save 180 lives if need
be but uh I flew back to uh Pennsylvania
once last year that was the time I was
on a flight to see a friend of mine who
just became a father and uh like all new
parents he pretends that he likes
fatherhood but I can tell he's sick of
it just by the way he talks about the
baby he oh it's great she's so cute but
she wakes up at 3:00 a.m. every night to
feed there's like nothing that you love
feeds ticks and vampires and parasites
feed things that suck the life out of
you nobody talks that way about
something they love it's never like oh
me and my wife just celebrated our
one-year anniversary I took her to Red
Lobster so she could
feed they have kids now I think that's
great i' like to have kids someday I
don't know if you guys have kids it
seems fun but it's a big responsibility
and it's a much bigger responsibility
than it used to be because they don't
stay kids forever and no one ever moves
out of their parents house
anymore so you're going to have a kid
for 12 years and then a teenager for 6
years and then for the rest of your life
you just have an
adult just some balding jerk with a
mustache who's as big as you are and
gets DUIs and
stuff no one prepares you for that part
they're always like watch out for the
Terrible twos they're never like watch
out for the divorced
[Applause]
41s I like kids though I like babies I
saw a pro-life billboard the other day
it said babies get hiccups even before
they're born which is true and I do not
support abortion but I bet a visit to
the clinic would scare those hiccups
away like that one CU a pro-life joke
offends pro-life people just alienates
everybody no one knows what to think of
me
anymore more political
jokes it's hard to do political jokes
right now CU this country is so divided
we're fighting over so many stupid
things like transgender bathrooms people
arguing over whether they're transgender
people should use the bathroom that
matches their biological sex or the
bathroom that matches their gender
identity and both sides are upset
because they don't want to use a public
bathroom with someone who makes them
uncomfortable which makes perfect sense
unless you've ever used a public
bathroom there's always someone who
makes you
uncomfortable there's always a stranger
who wants to talk while you're peeing or
there's a homeless person using the sink
as a shower or someone makes eye contact
through that Gap in the stall
door or there's a kid who's almost 12
but still pulls his pants all the way
down to
pee in the ladies room
we never were getting the genders that
right in the first
place no using a public bathroom and
being comfortable is not a real
experience anyone has there's no reason
to take that fight to the Supreme Court
like the justices are in their 80s they
have enough of their own bathroom issues
to deal
with but that's what we're fighting
about like transgender women don't want
to use the men's rum and then a lot of
other women don't want those transgender
people in their bathroom because they're
biologically men so what it all comes
down to is no one wants to use the
bathroom with
men like as divisive as the issue is we
all agree that men and their bodies are
disgusting and it's true men's bodies
are way more disgusting than women's
bodies just look at the sexy outfits
people wear sexiest thing a woman can
wear is lingerie which is basically
nothing at all sexiest thing a man can
wear is a three-piece
suit just layers and layers of material
covering every inch of his horrible
[Applause]
body then just to be safe it's tied
around his neck to make sure it doesn't
fall
off you think it's weird that women
carry an entire purse with them
everywhere they go and all guys have is
a wallet like ladies why do you need
something 10 times bigger to carry 30%
less
money
[Applause]
in case you haven't figured out I am a
republican but it's too late for anyone
to hate me you already laughed at some
of the
jokes it's rare to find conservative
comedians in La I do these jokes and
I'll get people come up to me after a
show one time this woman comes up to me
and she goes are you doing a character
up there or do you really mean all that
ignorant stuff you
said I'm like relax of course I don't
mean all that ignorant stuff I said the
real Adam loves Red
[Applause]
Lobster but they're all politically
correct out there you know they call
everything racist now there's even this
stereotype that NASCAR fans are all
rednecks and racists which I don't think
is fair because I don't think NASCAR
fans can help
it I don't I mean people Le into the
cello are cellists and people earn to
gymnastics are gymnasts so naturally
people earn to
racing
[Applause]
our racist if anyone's still working on
it do you like living out in Hollywood
you know theyve weird they weird
political issues out there though they
ban plastic straws because apparently
they take a 100 million years to
decompose so they've replace them with
paper straws which decompose before I
finish my
drink my only options are either kill a
sea turtle or have compost in the bottom
of my
cup but no it's good they got those
straws out of the ocean to make room for
these
[Applause]
masks we a big homeless crisis out there
right now I actually got an argument
with a homeless person the other day it
wasn't even over money he was sitting on
the side walk and he goes hey buddy you
got the time and I said no and I kept
walking and he goes what do you mean
jerk you're wearing a watch and I turn
around I'm like I'm not a jerk my watch
battery is dead I don't know what time
it is and he goes well why are you
wearing it I was like cuz I don't need
the watch to tell time there's clocks
everywhere the watch is just an
expensive status symbol to show that I
have more money than you're right I'm a
[Laughter]
jerk I do like living out there but the
earthquake still scare me cuz I grew up
on the East Coast so I have no idea what
you're supposed to do to stay safe in an
earthquake ever since moving to the West
Coast I've only ever heard two pieces of
advice first thing I've been told is
that you're supposed to stand in a
doorway second thing I've been told is
no that's not true you're not supposed
to stand in a doorway and that's all
anyone will tell
me no one has any idea what you're
actually supposed to do in an earthquake
then someone tried to tell me you're
supposed to lay on the ground I was like
the ground is what's trying to kill
you but I keep hearing that we're due
for the big one and I want to be
prepared so I went out and I researched
it and I got this stuff it's called
earthquake putty it's like a super
adhesive for your furniture
and I used it to glue googly eyes to all
my
stuff it won't save my life it'll just
look kind of funny as I'm
dying live on my own right now but I
want to get a pet and I want to get a
dog and everyone goes oh you got to get
one from a shelter they go you got to
get a dog from the shelter so I went to
the shelter to check it out and you
wouldn't believe all the breeds you can
pick from you can get like a husky
pitbull mix or a golden retriever
pitbull mix or chihuahua pitbull
mix if you're not a dog person they have
kittens and parakeet that are pitbull
mix not that there's anything wrong with
pit bulls like my neighbor has one and
it's adorable even has one of those
little stick figure families on the back
of his car and he added a little Pitbull
and then two days later he scraped off
one of the
kids some people try to defend pites
they say oh they're the sweetest dog in
the world they just have a bad
reputation then every time I turn on the
TV a pitbull is doing something horrible
it's always like pitbull attacks jogger
pitbull bites child or Pitbull's
collaborating with R
Kelly it's probably some newer rapper I
could update that with like I don't know
the rappers now I just know they have
face tattoos everywhere which is weird
you know like 15 years ago I was like
why would anybody want a stupid face
tattoo like Mike Tyson and now I find
myself going why can't you just get a
nice face tattoo like Mike
Tyson just a good oldfashioned
conservative face tattoo he could land a
job interview with that or one of those
tear drops that says you killed someone
something nice now these rappers have
like lines under their cheeks and
squiggles on their foreheads and numbers
under their eyes it looks like they went
out and got one stupid face tattoo and
then to teach them a lesson their dad
made them get an entire pack of stupid
face
tattoos I'm kidding they don't have
dads
I got to get something to eat after this
I I saw there's a McDonald's nearby the
McDonald's sign is always weird to me
because it says 99 billion served but I
looked it up and there's only 7.5
billion people on Earth which means
McDonald's food has killed 91.5 billion
people we love to eat in this country I
read a study that said Americans
nowadays get more excited about eating
than they do about
intimacy someone's all on board for
that who are you here
with no leave you guys out of it no that
sounded crazy to me at first that people
like eating more than intimacy I thought
about is reflecting the metaphors we use
you know like kissing his first base and
fooling around his second and third base
and then going all the way is a home run
but two eggs bacon hash browns and
pancakes is a grand
slam a lot of denus fans here tonight
I asked a friend if he wanted to meet me
at Denny's for dinner and he goes no I
haven't showered all day and I smell bad
I was like have you been to Denny's
before never stopped anyone from going
it's not a fancy place like Red
Lobster all right thanks a lot you guys
that's my time thank you dve bar
comedy